CONTACT

• New Zealand

+64 21 132 4388

mitchell.burton@gmail.com

n https://www.linkedin.com/in/mit chell-lawson-burton/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am an experienced agile leader that looks to enhance the productivity and impact of those around me. I have been a Senior Engineer and Tech Lead of high preforming agile teams for several years. I demonstrate servant leadership and leading by example while empowering and coaching those around me. I have years of experience of working in globally distributed teams.

SKILLS

- JavaScript / TypeScript
- React
- Node.js
- C# / .NET
- Next.js
- AWS
- CI/CD
- Service Orientated Architecture
- Microservices
- API Development
- Agile
- DevEx

MITCHELL LAWSON-BURTON

EXPERIENCE

Lead Software Engineer GetSetUp

01/2022 - Present

- Developed the <u>GetSetUp Anywhere</u> product, allowing partners to embed GetSetUp video content, leading to substantial revenue impact.
- Integrated in-class user chat with Zendesk tickets, optimizing support efficiency and reducing the unit cost of classes.
- Established a remote communication charter for the team, emphasizing async communication and open communication principles.
- Built an OAuth integration between GetSetUp and Circle.so, enabling a cost-effective experiment to grow a 55+ focused community.

Principal Engineer Livestock Improvement Corporation (LIC) 11/2021 - 03/2022

- Provided key technical leadership for LIC's flagship web app: MINDA Live, a BI and farm management tool.
- Architected RESTful API services and web front end ends.

Senior Software Engineer Livestock Improvement Corporation (LIC) 02/2017 - 10/2021

- Architected RESTful API services and web front end ends.
- Responsible for the creation of the Principal Engineer role.
- Designed the interview process for engineering recruitment.

Web Developer MetOcean Solutions

07/2016 - 02/2017

- Reduced downtime and increased developer productivity.
- Introduced automated setup of production and test webservers.
- Created a deployment process.
- Created BDD contract tests for the WXTiles API.

Analyst Developer Enlighten Designs

01/2013 - 01/2016

- Became Tech Lead for an agile development team.
- Surfaced several sales opportunities to Enlighten.

EDUCATION

Graduate Diploma (Philosophy) University of Waikato, 2013

Bachelor of Science with First Class Honours (Computer Science) University of Waikato, 2012